I'm ready to crush this.
Let's go!
I'm sure it feels that way, but he has a reason for everything.
I can't give up on being a forward.
It's who I am, and I'm not budging.
I'll give Fullback a try, but if I want out, I'll need to know.
What he was thinking!
What the hell?!
Oh, Tachibana's like 40 miles away.
The field seems so much bigger than before.
Huh?
The shuffle.
If you can manage to get that down,
then I don't care if you go and join the attack or stay out here.
The ball's all the way upfield.
This is not the time to be defending.
I'm pushing up.
Owie! Get back here!
Wait, what?
You said it didn't matter if I stayed here or joined the attack.
Idiot, look at the other wing.
See how Masako, the right back, is already pushing up?
If the far right back goes forward, the left back drops into the middle, remember?
Togashi and I have already shuffled across, so you stay put.
Don't just push up without checking to see what your teammates are doing first.
Hey, Otomo!
Oh, damn it all!
They're coming!
Not that this is something I didn't already know,
but I absolutely hate defending!
I hate it more than anything!
Huh?
They're coming down the left.
Does that mean they're targeting me?
Okay, shift across and cover the middle.
Got it!
All right, you guys, I'm ready!
Come at me, you punks!
I'm waiting for you!
What the hell are you doing, Ewie?
You're supposed to be shuffling, idiot!
That's how I got here?
Look!
I shuffled across like you said!
That is not what you're doing!
He can't be serious!
If I keep moving further across, I'll be leaving the wing wide open!
It's like you have zero awareness at all of what you need to play defense.
I didn't know I had to teach you the basic rules of each position.
Unbelievable.
You can't play the same way here you play up front, Ewie.
When you run out, no one is behind you to guard the goal.
Repeat after me.
There is no one.
Think you got it?
Repeat that to yourself until the next ball comes.
Ashito!
You aren't shuffling into the middle at all, man.
We have to tighten up more.
Make that the priority.
Uh-huh, uh...
Ashito!
What?
This is the first time I've even touched the ball today!
Let's try to build some momentum!
Let's go!
Don't just push up without checking to see what your teammates are doing first!
Hang on, Masako!
He's not moving up.
He's staying put.
I'm out!
Yeah?
Look out!
The A-team defender is pressing!
The midfielder, too!
I'm surrounded!
Ashito, put the ball out!
Nah, it's too late!
Akutsu!
He's cutting into the space on the left!
There are still two forwards hanging out in the middle.
I can't cover him!
Whether I push up or stay back, I gotta base that decision on everyone else.
And I'm supposed to shuffle across.
But I don't know how far to go in!
I'm not meant for this position!
And I'm absolutely bored out of my mind!
What the hell's that old man thinking?
He was dead wrong!
There's no way I can do this!
What's up, guys?
You think the poor B-team is gonna be okay?
We don't have much room to talk since we lost Yoshitsune.
But your team's fallen apart.
It's like you guys totally forgot how to play when Taita and Nagano aren't around.
And what's with making a complete scrub, the new defender?
Whatever you do, you don't want to get dumped from the Tokyo Metropolis League.
Here's some advice for free, Aoi.
Me to you.
Why don't you go back to your dorm room as soon as possible and start packing up your bags?
The sooner the better.
That lack of talent isn't a good look on anyone.
There's nothing fulfilling about playing as a fullback.
It's so boring.
I can't do this anymore.
It's not right.
This isn't where I ought to be.
Rowan, to the right!
Out there.
That's where I belong.
My spot.
I want to score.
Hey, Aoi, stay put.
Masaka's already pushing up.
Are we going to have to go over this again?
You know?
When you were playing forward, you always seemed like a player with wider vision.
Is that something that just goes away if you're not feeling it, or what?
This isn't where I ought to be.
Shut up, dammit!
You're in the middle of a game.
Stop freaking out and focus.
Incoming!
Ashito, they got the ball!
You're supposed to shuffle across!
Here comes the shot!
Block it!
Optimo!
It's not over yet.
The ball's not clear!
What is up with this guy's body?
Dammit!
Went to their side again!
Nice clearance!
Corner kick!
Ultimo, are you okay?
Oh, come on, you guys.
No rough stuff today.
Oh, jeez.
This is just only a minigame.
But hey, I guess you all hate to lose.
Am I right?
I'm sorry.
I should have been defending there.
Huh?
How about we all play defense today?
I've got a bunch of unused defensive skills that I'd love to show off.
So yeah, this is all for me.
Anyway, we're good.
You should apologize to Togashi.
He wants to play upfield, but he's been too busy defending today.
You know?
Alright, let's restart.
Hey, guys, quit pushing.
I said stop that.
We can't afford any more injuries, so you two cut it out.
Uh, Togashi?
What?
I, uh, I'm sorry.
Because of me?
You can't go upfield like you usually do.
What in the hell?
You think you have any effect on what I do, knucklehead?
I'm the only one who influences how I play.
Fukuda told me I needed to work on my defensive skills, so I am.
I apologize to Otomo, not me.
This isn't where I ought to be.
I know that.
I said I know!
Stop it!
This isn't where I ought to be.
I said I get it!
I get it.
So don't let yourself become a burden.
On your friends!
Farsight!
They're targeting Akutsu!
Even further than that?
But who's it going to?
It's the other flank!
Crap.
They piled players up on the left, hoping this would happen.
Your team's 1 yen coins.
10 yens are the opposition.
You scored because of all the loose balls you picked up.
Were you aware of that?
Did he ride the flight of the ball?
No way!
This was more than that.
The moment he made the corner kick, he started running straight at me.
Your dumbass keeps making dumbass moves, and it's just disgusting!
Go!
Tachibana!
There's only one defender!
It's our best chance to counter!
Okay, time's up!
Yo, B-team.
You have got to ditch that crap defender.
He's only being forced to play defense now to make up the numbers.
But he'll quit soon enough.
You shouldn't hang around talentless, spoiled crybabies.
You could end up just like him if you're not careful.
Like I said, make sure you don't get dropped from the league.
That's literally the only job the second team has.
You should really start worrying about yourselves.
You guys only managed to score one goal against our makeshift talentless team.
What's that say about you?
You're lost without Yoshitsune!
At least that's what it looks like from out here.
Am I right or am I right?
I guess weaklings have to surround themselves with other weaklings.
Huh?
I know that people say it all the time, but I hope you sad sacks haven't been taking it to heart too much.
About how youth teams aren't as strong mentally as high school teams are.
Damn it.
That last clearance.
Why didn't it get to Tachibana?
We could have scored easily.
Feels like your tempo and rhythm are all over the place, huh?
Well, don't overthink it.
And something to remember about the shuffle.
Even if leaving the wing wide open is a big risk, always think about tightening up centrally first.
As long as we have the numbers we need in the middle,
the other team attacking down the flanks isn't going to be that big of a deal.
Well, you'll pick it up soon enough.
So, you brought a girl to training?
Hey, now.
I'm the kind of guy who likes to keep his private life off the soccer field.
Yeah, sure.
Anyway, your shuffle has a way to go, but that last move wasn't bad.
What last move?
Are you talking about the messed up kick?
No.
Before that.
For real.
Your vision's really wide.
Huh?
What do you mean, my vision?
Your lack of self-awareness is intriguing.
You should work on that and be more intentional with it.
You'll have more fun.
I also think it'll help you be less erratic, which could benefit you in all kinds of situations.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Maybe study Kuribayashi's place.
Have you watched him much?
Huh?
There's some things in his game that you could incorporate into your own.
He's always using techniques to help increase the options he has available to him.
I bet you could increase your options as well.
I think if you do that, playing defense will be a lot more fun.
Later.
Wait.
Oh.
Oh...
Yuma.
Hey, what's up?
Togashi, you too.
Can you tell me something?
Why is Aoi playing as a fullback?
The two of you were the first ones to recognize the unique ability that Aoi has.
So then, you must have some idea what's going on.
Why was he suddenly switched to fullback?
What was the purpose?
Is this manager Fukuda?
Is he trying to tell us something?
I'd like to know your honest thoughts on it.
If he's trying to convey a message, I hope you'll tell me.
Ugh.
What the hell are you yakking about?
I'm too beat up for all this.
I get that you're the owner's daughter and all, but damn.
I don't have time to sit here and indulge you nosy rich people.
Now go on home.
Togashi, I can't let you tear her down like this, so I'll fill you in.
Someday, she's gonna be your manager.
And just because she's never played the game doesn't mean she can't be a manager.
Whole new world.
Must be a nice way to live.
Being born to the owner of a soccer team.
Just so we are clear, I never said I wanted to be Esperion's manager.
Which means, this has nothing to do with whose daughter I am.
I want to work with a men's soccer team.
That much is true.
But not a leftover.
It's important to me to build my own career.
Using my own ideas.
Even if it means starting with a smaller team at first.
That's what I've dreamed from myself.
Oh.
It never gets old!
Doesn't matter how many times I hear it.
I love listening to her talk about it.
She's been reciting that fairy tale to us for years!
Okay, fine. I'll tell you.
But let me hear your thoughts first.
Why do you think you made Ashito become a defender?
If you meant what you said, then tell me.
I did, yes.
I'll be honest with you.
At first, I didn't think Aoi was youth team material.
It did not matter to me what position he played.
He'll be a liability to the team.
But after watching the game against Seikyo Hai, I changed my mind.
His vision is truly incredible.
Up till then, I'd never seen a player like him.
Ain't that the truth.
Ashito was brought in to be a fullback cause his vision can be put to best use there.
I'm positive that's why he got in.
Cause let's face it, dude was not the best player that tried out that day.
But that's Fukuda for you.
Please know I haven't changed my mind about our discussion.
I still don't agree with the theories you introduced.
They're not based on scientific fact.
That's a bit of a leap.
He can't know all of your placements.
I hope you understand.
It's impossible.
We should avoid introducing unscientific theories and hypotheses into any sport.
Aoi can memorize some players' positions.
And even predict the movements of others.
But that's it.
That's the scope of his vision.
And for what it's worth, I don't believe his talent is best utilized as a forward.
I honestly think the best position for Aoi is midfielder.
Attacking midfielder.
Or at least a deep line one.
Something central.
But defender makes no sense.
I mean defense isn't remotely in his wheelhouse.
I respect manager Fukuda so very much.
But I have no idea what he was thinking.
I would like to know, though.
Uh, miss?
Do you mean her?
Here's what I've learned.
You really love soccer, don't you?
I've never heard a woman go on about soccer like that.
Oh, yes.
Your passion's legit.
Practically dripping out your nose.
It's too bad.
You're wasting a golden opportunity.
What?
Yeah, I agree.
Honestly, I couldn't care less why Ashito has to be a fullback or whatever.
But I do know I'll never get these past five minutes back where I could've been-
Wait!
Please elaborate on what you just said.
So first of all, you're trying to convince me that what we said in the classroom was unscientific.
Well, I was watching this show a while back.
And they had this ex-Spanish international guy on it as a guest.
They were trying to scientifically prove how wide his field of vision was.
They strapped a small camera to him.
Made him play a match.
And then asked him to review the footage afterwards.
Then they would stop the footage part of the way through.
While it was off, he was told he had to draw the positions of the players at the moment that was last on screen as accurately as possible.
They did the same experiment with other players.
The best they could do was come up with maybe three of them tops.
Some of them barely remembered where they were themselves.
But this guy, he got every player's position perfect.
Both his team and the others.
I know of that experiment.
But that was the product of his training, built on top of his natural talent.
Only special people like him could-
The thing is, none of it matters to the players.
We don't got time for science.
All we care about is what's happening on the field, and we trust our own senses.
You know, Henri, when you were talking about how you didn't think Ashito should be playing fullback,
that you think he ought to be playing centrally, attacking midfielder,
all it made me see is that you don't know that much about soccer.
You seem to think that fullbacks are only there to support, like the Lance and Shogi or something.
Middle's the most important.
That's just your unconscious bias.
No one knows what's up with old man Fukuda's mind.
But we're not talking about him.
You gotta loosen up your thoughts, friend, or you'll miss the big picture.
Soccer's freer! It does what it wants!
That said, I don't want to leave you hanging with what I think about Ashito's on-field position future,
or why I think manager Fukuda reassigned him to play fullback instead of being a forward.
I don't know your opinion, but I bet it's the same as mine.
One, two, three!
Playmaker!
Next time on Awashi, just like you.